[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the life span of a rhino?", "correct_answer": "40 years", "incorrect_answers": ["15 years", "20 years", "30 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This monster, who is classified under the family, Homolycanth Ropus, really has a thing about silver bullets. By what other name do we know the character, Lawrence Talbort?", "correct_answer": "The Wolfman", "incorrect_answers": ["The Zombie", "The Beast", "The Mummy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Compared to men, women are much more likely to fall into this group in regards to their color vision.", "correct_answer": "Tetrachromats", "incorrect_answers": ["Color-deficient", "Dichromats", "Color-blind"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is wrong about the reproduction of scorpions?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Most scorpions reproduce through parthenogenesis.", "Most scorpion species are hermaphrodites.", "Most scorpions reproduce asexually."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Robert De Niro won his first Academy Award for Best Actor for his performance in this movie.", "correct_answer": "Raging Bull", "incorrect_answers": ["The Godfather, Part II", "Taxi Driver", "The Deer Hunter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Chevy Nova sold poorly in Mexico because no va means doesnt go in Spanish.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous news reporter was honored with the Purple Heart after he was killed by a Japanese sniper in 1945?", "correct_answer": "Ernie Pyle", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack Harrison", "Roger Vanderbilt", "Mason Hall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Fletch, while trying to find out more about Alan Stanwyk, Fletch ends up in the morgue and passes out. He wakes up in the Records room and asks for what album?", "correct_answer": "The Beatles - White Album", "incorrect_answers": ["The Eagles - Hotel California", "Cream - Wheels of Fire", "AC/DC - Highway to Hell"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Hydrogen?", "correct_answer": "H", "incorrect_answers": ["Hy", "Hr", "Hd"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The vast majority of tornadoes in the world occur in the Tornado Alley region which is located in this country.", "correct_answer": "The United States", "incorrect_answers": ["Indonesia", "Mexico", "Australia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This character from Cheech and Chongs Next Movie has a date with Cheeh and he is dreaming about her, while waiting for her to come in his house.", "correct_answer": "Donna", "incorrect_answers": ["Jade", "Sylvia", "Maria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does liquid iron float on liquid nickel?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}]